this thing
on hey Miss PS if you find this recording don't
feel bad about recording don't feel bad about this part
of the journey is
this part of the journey is end just the record
Being a drift in space with zero promise of rescue
is space with zero promise of rescue is more fun
than it pounds food and water ran out 4 days
ago oxygen will run out Tom longrow ago oxygen will run out Tom longrow morning
that be it when I drift off will dream about
you it's always
Thanos did exactly what he said was going to do
he wiped out 50% of all living
creatures we lost all of
us we lost friends family
a part of
ourselves this is the fight of our ourselves this is the fight of our lives
this is going to work lives this is going to work Steve
I know it is cuz I don't know what I'm
going to do if it doesn't
hi uh is anyone home this Scott Lang is we
met a few years ago at the airport in Germany
got really big is this an old message Ant-Man and
I know you that it's the front door that's me
Can you buzz in